{
	"fibonacci": [
		{
			"answer": "enemy has been spotted at the west gate, requesting backup.",
			"question": "fogpd paf wmhy gobfspn ao yhj bohs uagf, fttmzfbdqe cabkto."
		},
		{
			"answer": "requesting backup at north camp, we've been ambushed.",
			"question": "sfsxjagdvj maqjhb as yymyh harz, ld'jr cstq aewhachb."
		},
		{
			"answer": "requesting airlift at north front, 7 survivors.",
			"question": "sfsxjagdvj atfkvrs ae xjwtm kbdmh, 7 fvfklnjea."
		},
		{
			"answer": "critical system failure on alpha-6, requesting landing.",
			"question": "dskwnkay ngvesl saukfbz tn aqura-6, gdehfgilfb yavyllh."
		},
		{
			"answer": "enemy tanker has been captured.",
			"question": "fogpd baafmu sag arqm nazozrji."
		},
		{
			"answer": "requesting backup, the front-line has been ambushed.",
			"question": "sfsxjagdvj maqjhb, sso awosy-vxms uat pthf ahocnkce."
		},
		{
			"answer": "thermal signatures have been detected at the east gate.",
			"question": "uigurat fdoqaeiqre gago wjes ioidqgfr ai wzz raao jarf."
		},
		{
			"answer": "the mid-field barracks have been infiltrated.",
			"question": "uig pnl-sdmoo paqeaojd raqj bjjx xmtvmhgawwy."
		},
		{
			"answer": "we have been shot, retreat to the base camp.",
			"question": "xf jayj jrzv vscs, eqscoao yo ymo qars pand."
		},
		{
			"answer": "requesting arms in the north-camp...i repeat, requesting arms in the north-camp",
			"question": "sfsxjagdvj acar vz sso itrym-mabo...w efdtaw, jzdczvrjmg aqlq fi luj flgfi-paaq"
		},
		{
			"answer": "missile launch will occur exactly at noon on the next saturday.",
			"question": "njuvntr gacqnv vvxk zmxzr jcamikm ag ocdq gi gpz qcys sastpaat."
		},
		{
			"answer": "rations have been shipped to the front lines.",
			"question": "saukrsa uaqm epsm fthazzi tt yrt efboh alfzf."
		},
		{
			"answer": "several incoming planes detected into the western front.",
			"question": "tfxhwat vikrxwmt bkayon ieyjmidr vohd wzz jmnwcsm fqnlq."
		},
		{
			"answer": "eastern front cryptographic integrity compromised.",
			"question": "fatvhwv smwqe qqlbszqmauhnh scsstswib ujzxmrkjrec."
		},
		{
			"answer": "it appears that our enemies have managed to decipher our communications.",
			"question": "ju arsjazf opaw ziq rzdxszx haaj wacafsq uc shudcpzu mvq cnlkriapayalce."
		},
		{
			"answer": "new encryption system will be used from midnight. details will be sent via encrypted post.",
			"question": "ofy hsketxwtcm fkreoh biqq lt tgre tgre hvlileis. ddsagin ovqd yt efah wxa usxrtkjpe bbrf."
		},
		{
			"answer": "the enemy has been spotted at the southern front.",
			"question": "uig hsmzt pav msda eozdojd ay yrt rchuvtuf aewiw."
		},
		{
			"answer": "fighters have been dispatched to enemy position at the southern front.",
			"question": "gjikymen payp pdrz ctckaycmjn in safan sgnvbdrl au shd rmrozrwf cgaog."
		},
		{
			"answer": "reconaissance craft spotted above west camp.",
			"question": "sfersaqfnavfp qqasf rayoyei agykd krth raph."
		},
		{
			"answer": "missile interception system failed on north front.",
			"question": "njuvntr dvwpfbrbstyi xyxyob eawyfr dq fjebc ippmt."
		}
	],
	"caesar": [
		{
			"answer": "does anyone have eyes on the falcon?",
			"question": "juky gteutk ngbk keky ut znk lgriut?"
		},
		{
			"answer": "there has been a security breach in the far camp.",
			"question": "uifsf ibt cffo b tfdvsjuz csfbdi jo uif gbs dbnq."
		},
		{
			"answer": "alfa-zulu in the air, ready to strike.",
			"question": "bmgb-avmv jo uif bjs, sfbez up tusjlf."
		},
		{
			"answer": "mission aborted, return back to the airbase.",
			"question": "soyyout ghuxzkj, xkzaxt hgiq zu znk goxhgyk."
		},
		{
			"answer": "radio check...radio check... loud and clear.",
			"question": "wfint hmjhp...wfint hmjhp... qtzi fsi hqjfw."
		},
		{
			"answer": "bogey at your left... roger that.",
			"question": "dqiga cv aqwt nghv... tqigt vjcv."
		},
		{
			"answer": "target confirmed, requesting confirmation to engage.",
			"question": "ubshfu dpogjsnfe, sfrvftujoh dpogjsnbujpo up fohbhf."
		},
		{
			"answer": "eagle-1 fox-2 do you copy?",
			"question": "iekpi-1 jsb-2 hs csy gstc?"
		},
		{
			"answer": "the bogey has been eliminated, over and out.",
			"question": "xli fskic lew fiir ipmqmrexih, sziv erh syx."
		},
		{
			"answer": "does any have eyes on the armed bird?",
			"question": "fqgu cpa jcxg gagu qp vjg ctogf dktf?"
		},
		{
			"answer": "missile interception commencing on the north front.",
			"question": "njttjmf joufsdfqujpo dpnnfodjoh po uif opsui gspou."
		},
		{
			"answer": "enemy craft spotted at the eastern front.",
			"question": "mvmug kzinb axwbbml ib bpm miabmzv nzwvb."
		},
		{
			"answer": "missile silo access codes regenerated.",
			"question": "qmwwmpi wmps eggiww gshiw vikirivexih."
		},
		{
			"answer": "satellite communications disrupted.",
			"question": "vdwhoolwh frppxqlfdwlrqv glvuxswhg."
		},
		{
			"answer": "north front barricade breached, requesting backup.",
			"question": "opsui gspou cbssjdbef csfbdife, sfrvftujoh cbdlvq."
		},
		{
			"answer": "attempt at decrypting enemy communications has failed.",
			"question": "fyyjruy fy ijhwduynsl jsjrd htrrzsnhfyntsx mfx kfnqji."
		},
		{
			"answer": "enemy attempt to decrypt communications. stay alert.",
			"question": "lultf haaltwa av kljyfwa jvttbupjhapvuz. zahf hslya."
		},
		{
			"answer": "central control to alpha-6, landing granted.",
			"question": "kmvbzit kwvbzwt bw itxpi-6, tivlqvo ozivbml."
		},
		{
			"answer": "enemy ship sunk at west beach.",
			"question": "jsjrd xmnu xzsp fy bjxy gjfhm."
		},
		{
			"answer": "our generals have been captured. possible communications breach.",
			"question": "vby nlulyhsz ohcl illu jhwabylk. wvzzpisl jvttbupjhapvuz iylhjo."
		}
	]
}
